Mss.B.F327
American Philosophical Society
- Rev. James Maury to Philip Ludwell, 1756 February 10; No. 923
- Rev. James Maury, 1763 December 14-1768 September 24; No. 924; 1.0 vol.
- Dr. John Mawney to Dr. _____ Stimson, 1777 September 30; No. 925
- Solomon Maxwell to Henry Hollingsworth, 1781 November 30; No. 926
- William Maxwell to Joseph Reed, 1779 March 7; No. 927
- George May to Staats Morris, 1798 March 31; No. 928
- Philip Mazzei to Thomas Jefferson, 1780 March 2; No. 929
- John Minthorn, 1780? January-February; No. 930
- Jasper Mead and Elizabeth Mead to Abraham Lockwood, 1802 May 6; No. 931
- Richard Kidder Meade to Alexander McDougall, 1779 June 21; No. 932
- New York City, Mechanics in Union and their Associates, 1776 April 16; No. 933
- Samuel Meers to James Habersham, 1789 May 6; No. 934
- Return Jonathan Meigs to John Sumner, 1780 October 9; No. 935
- District of Massachusetts, Port of Boston and Charlestown, 1797 May 5; No. 936
- District of Massachusetts, Port of Boston and Charlestown, 1797 September 12; No. 937
- John Mercer, 1755 January 11-1763 October; No. 938
- Joshua Mersereau to Abraham Skinner, 1780 October 18; No. 939
- Joshua Mersereau, 1780; No. 940
- Joshua Mersereau to the Council of the State of Massachusetts, 1780 February 28; No. 941
- Joshua Mersereau to the Council of the State of Massachusetts Bay, 1780 August 31; No. 942
- Thomas Mifflin to George Gray, 1783 November 23; No. 943
- Thomas Mifflin to Jabez Huntington, 1776 January 10; No. 944
- Thomas Mifflin to Artemus Ward, 1775 August 16; No. 945
- John Milton to ________, 1779 April 16; No. 946
- Regarding Benjamin Franklin, 1790 June 11; No. 947
- James Monroe to Mr. ______ Alexander, 1806 September 16; No. 948
- James Monroe to James Madison, 1786 November; No. 949
- James Monroe to Return Jonathan Meigs, 1822 April 13; No. 950
- James Monroe to Littleton W. Tazewell, 1806 November 14; No. 951
- James Monroe to ________, 1806 August 15; No. 952
- John Montresor, by order of Gen. Sir William Howe, 1776 December; No. 953
- Stephen Moore and John Barnwell to Nathanael Greene, 1781 May 18; No. 954
- United States, Continental Army, n.d.; No. 955
- Deborah Morris, guardian for John Morris Potts to Thomas Newark, 1783 January 9; No. 956
- Gouverneur Morris to Messrs. LeRoy, Bayard, and McEvers, 1802 March 28; No. 957
- Robert Morris to All whom it may concern, 1778 January 10; No. 958
- Robert Morris to Tench Francis, 1785 December 31; No. 959
- Robert Morris to John Adams, 1782 September 27; No. 960
- Robert Morris to Nathaniel Appleton, 1782 September 9; No. 961
- Robert Morris to John Barry, 1797 August 8; No. 962
- Robert Morris to Ephraim Blaine, 1781 December 4; No. 963
- Robert Morris to John Bradford, 1777 February 27; No. 964
- Robert Morris to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 September 27; No. 965
- Robert Morris to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 October 1; No. 966
- Robert Morris to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 October 7; No. 967
- Robert Morris to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 February 12; No. 968
- Robert Morris to Nathaniel Gorham, 1791 July 30; No. 969
- Robert Morris to George Harrison, 1798 May 21; No. 970
- Robert Morris to Henry Hollingsworth, 1779 November 16; No. 971
- Robert Morris to James McEvers, 1798 January 1; No. 972
- Robert Morris to James M. Marshall, 1798 April 27; No. 973
- Robert Morris to John Nicholson, 1793 August 3; No. 974
- Robert Morris to John Nicholson, 1798 June 11; No. 975
- Robert Morris to Messrs. Willem and Jan Willink, Nicholas and Jacob Van Staphorst, De la Lande and Fynje, 1784 February 12; No. 976
- Robert Morris to John Matteux and Company, 1784 April 22; No. 977
- Robert Morris, 1793 August-December; No. 978
- William Moultrie to the Commissioners of the Treasury, 1787 February 28; No. 979
- R______ Mowbray, Surgeon, 1775 June 21; No. 980
- James Moylan to John Brown, 1781 September 27; No. 981
- James Moylan to John Brown, 1782 January 1; No. 982
- Stephen Moylan to William Bartlett, 1775 November 15; No. 983
- Stephen Moylan to William Bartlett, 1775 December 10; No. 984
- Stephen Moylan to William Bartlett, 1776 April 4; No. 985
- Stephen Moylan to William Bartlett and John Glover, 1775 December 2; No. 986
- Frederick Augustus Conrad Muhlenberg to Dr. Benjamin Rush, 1789 May 8; No. 987
- John Peter Gabriel Muhlenburg to Robert Lawson, 1781 January 31; No. 988
- John Peter Gabriel Muhlenburg to Dr. Benjamin Rush, 1789 June 25; No. 989
- John Peter Gabriel Muhlenburg to ________, 1780 September 23; No. 990
- Hardy Murfree to Henry Hollingsworth, 1779 December 15; No. 991
- James Murray to Lord George Townshend, 1782 September 1; No. 992
- John Murray to Ephraim Bowen, 1779 July 23; No. 993
- Samuel Murray to Rufus King, 1801 March 24, 26; No. 994
- William Vans Murray to Robert Gilmore, Jr., 1803 June 20; No. 995
- William Vans Murray to Jean Luzac, 1800 February 5; No. 996
- ________ to "Gaston", 1806 April 4; No. 997
- France, Navy, 1780 May 5-July 22, 1782 August 25, 1783; No. 998
- Tench Coxe, 1797?; No. 999
- Abraham Neely to Edward Dunscomb, 1783 May 20; No. 1000
- Thomas Nelson, Jr. to Robert Lawson, 1781 September 2; No. 1001
- John Neufville, by Order of the General Committee to the Committee at Philadelphia, 1770 July 3; No. 1002
- Province of New Hampshire, House of Representatives, 1773 May 28; No. 1003
- State of New Hampshire, Committee of Safety to Moses Woodward, 1781 July 5; No. 1004
- State of New Hampshire, Committee of Safety to Moses Woodward, 1781 October 25; No. 1005
- State of New Hampshire House of Representatives, 1780 April 27; No. 1006
- State of New Jersey, Council of Safety, 1777 June 9; No. 1007
- Colony of New Jersey, Essex County Court to the sheriff, 1766 June 18; No. 1008
- Philip Smick, 1820 June 14; No. 1009
- John Sithian, 1827 June 15; No. 1010
- Province of New York, Governor William Tryon to Isaac Vrooman, 1772 July 17; No. 1011
- New York, Provincial Congress to the delegates for the Colony of New York in Continental Congress, 1775 June 28; No. 1012
- New York, City of Albany, Committee, 1793 September 27; No. 1013
- Abraham Yates, Jr., on behalf of the Common Council of Albany, N.Y. to Philip Schuyler, 1793 September 25; No. 1014
- State of New York, Council of Safety to George Clinton, 1777 June 4; No. 1015
- State of New York, Convention of Representatives, 1776 September 4; No. 1016
- New York Inspectors "to all the Friends of America in Philadelphia & else where", 1770 August 6; No. 1017
- Wilson Carey Nicholas to Alexander James Dallas?, 1808 September 14; No. 1018
- John Nicholson to William Young and others, 1798 March 9; No. 1019
- John Nicholson to David Allison, 1796 April 4, 15; No. 1020
- Asheton Humphreys, Notary Public, on behalf of Robert Morris to John Nicholson, 1797 January 24; No. 1021
- John Nicholson to Robert Morris, 1795 January 21; No. 1022
- John Nicholson to Robert Morris, 1795 April 21; No. 1023
- John Nicholson to Robert Morris, 1795 May 2; No. 1024
- Lewis Nicola to Edward Hand, 1781 May 26; No. 1025
- John Nicoll to ________, 1781 November 14; No. 1026
- John Nixon to John Nicholson, n.d.; No. 1027
- Louis-Marie, vicomte de Noailles to ________, 1796 January 12; No. 1028
- Louis-Marie, vicomte de Noailles to ________, 1796 April 19; No. 1029
- Lord Frederick North to ________, n.d.; No. 1030
- William North to Benjamin Walker, 1783 November; No. 1031
- North American Land Company to John Barker Church, 1795 May 28; No. 1032
- North American Land Company to Dr. Enoch Edwards, 1795 April 18; No. 1033
- State of North Carolina to the sheriff of Washington County, 1782 August; No. 1034
- State of North Carolina, Governor Richard Dobbs Spaight to James Greenlee, 1792 July 7; No. 1035
- Hugh Percy, Duke of Northumberland to A______ Todd, 1796 May 29; No. 1036
- John Nuttel to George Washington, 1797 March 17; No. 1037
- Joseph Ogden and Miles Hillborn, 1779 December 16; No. 1038
- Andrew Oliver to Edward Hutchinson, 1742 December 29; No. 1039
- John Oliver to Thomas Hancock, 1755 December 22; No. 1040
- Jacques O'Moran to ________, 1792 April 27; No. 1041
- Richard Onslow to Charles? Harrison, 1778 March 20; No. 1042
- United States, Continental Army, Gen. William Heath's Division, 1776 October 6-29; No. 1043; 1.0 vol.
- Samuel Osgood and Walter Livingston to William Ellery, 1787 January 27; No. 1044
- Regarding James Otis, Jr. and others, 1760 August-1761 February; No. 1045; 1.0 vol.
- Regarding Thomas Paine, 1793?; No. 1046
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, No. 1047
  Microfilm target that describes the following twenty-one letters.
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1774 June 30; No. 1048
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1775 March 5; No. 1049
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1777 June 9; No. 1050
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1778 January 5; No. 1051
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1778 March 23, 26; No. 1052
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1781 January 30, February 1; No. 1053
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1783 April 12; No. 1054
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1783 May 13; No. 1055
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1783 August 20; No. 1056
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1786 July 22; No. 1057
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1786 August 12; No. 1058
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1787 July 7; No. 1059
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1789 October 5; No. 1060
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1789 December 24; No. 1061
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1790 July 13; No. 1062
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1791 March 22, 29, April 12; No. 1063
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1791 September 5; No. 1064
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1792 October 26; No. 1065
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1794 March 15; No. 1066
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1795 June 26; No. 1067
- Thomas Paine to Dr. Samuel Adams, 1796 April 21; No. 1068
- William Palfrey to General ________, 1776 November 13; No. 1069
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette for Jacques Jouen, 1790 October 1; No. 1070
- Anna M. Parker to John Brooks, 1779?; No. 1071
- Frederick Parker to Nahum Parker, 1780 November 4; No. 1072
- Sir Peter Parker to John Murray, Lord Dunmore?, 1776 May 1; No. 1073
- Richard Parker to Robert Carter, 1781 October 30; No. 1074
- William Parker to Paul Henry Curry, 1780 December 22; No. 1075
- Thomas Passmore, 1799 April 2; No. 1076
- James Paterson to all concerned, 1778 January 15; No. 1077
- James Paterson to Lord George Townshend, 1778 October 13; No. 1078
- John Patton and David Lenox to the President John Dickinson and the Supreme Executive Council of Pennsylvania, 1783 November 29; No. 1079
- Nathaniel Peabody to Henry Laurens, 1779 December 17; No. 1080
- Stephen Peabody, 1778 July; No. 1081
- James Pearson to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 August 15; No. 1082
- William Peck to Henry Jackson, 1778 September 13; No. 1083
- William Peck to Henry Jackson, 1778 September 16; No. 1084
- William Peck to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 1; No. 1085
- William Peck to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 1; No. 1086
- William Peck to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 30; No. 1087
- Society of Friends, Philadelphia, 1775 January 24; No. 1089
- Society of Friends, Philadelphia, 1776 January 20; No. 1090
- Nathaniel Pendleton to ________, 1785 May 4; No. 1091
- John Penn to Peter Stephen du Ponceau, 1825 September 1; No. 1092
- John Penn, Sr. to John Penn, Jr., 1778; No. 1093
- Israel Pemberton to ________, 1777 November 13; No. 1088
- Richard Penn to Arthur Lee, 1775 November 12; No. 1094
- James Alexander, 1746/47 January 21; No. 1095
- Penn Estates in Pennsylvania, n.d.; No. 1096
- Province of Pennsylvania Assembly to Thomas Smith, 1776 April 19; No. 1097
- Province of Pennsylvania House of Assembly, 1776 April 6; No. 1098
- State of Pennsylvania, Lottery, 1795 May 18; No. 1099
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Governor Thomas McKean to James Donalianus LeRoy de Chaumont, 1783 August 18; No. 1100
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Governor Thomas Mifflin to Robert Morris, 1794 December 2; No. 1101
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Governor Thomas McKean to Philip Nicklin and Robert E. Griffith, 1805 April 18; No. 1102
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, President Joseph Reed to William Kerlin, 1780 May 17; No. 1103
- Charles Biddle to David Rittenhouse, 1786 May 3; No. 1104
- Thomas Wharton, Jr., by order of the Council of Safety for the State of Pennsylvania to the Committee of Inspection and Observation for Salem County, N.J., 1776 August 2; No. 1105
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Court of Admirality to the wardens of the Port of Philadelphia, 1784 November 3; No. 1106
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Governor Thomas McKean to David Jackson, 1800 September 15; No. 1107
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Governor Thomas McKean to David Jackson, 1800 September 2; No. 1108
- Province of Pennsylvania, House of Assembly, 1776 April 6; No. 1109
- Province of Pennsylvania, House of Assembly, 1774 January 22; No. 1110
- John Moor, 1780 September 4; No. 1111
- Joseph Reed to the auditors of public accounts, 1781 February 2; No. 1112
- Joseph Reed to George Clinton, 1781 February 26; No. 1113
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Executive Council to Barnabus Binney, 1786 November 30; No. 1114
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Executive Council, John Dickinson, President to David Jackson, 1785 April 18; No. 1115
- Joseph Reed to David Rittenhouse, 1781 March 3; No. 1116
- Thomas Wharton, Jr. to David Rittenhouse, 1777 August 21; No. 1117
- Joseph Reed to David Rittenhouse, 1781 January 3; No. 1118
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Executive Council John Dickinson, President, 1783 September 13; No. 1119
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Executive Council Joseph Reed, President, 1781 April 19; No. 1120
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Executive Council Joseph Reed, President, 1781 April 27; No. 1121
- Pennsylvania War Office, 1777 May 2; No. 1122
- United States, Pension Office, 1820s; No. 1123
- Rev. Richard Peters to his brother William Peters, 1776 February 9, 29; No. 1124
- Richard Peters to Henry Hollongsworth, 1779 December 17; No. 1125
- Richard Peters to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 May 3; No. 1126
- Richard Peters to Thomas Smith, 1781 March 21; No. 1127
- Richard Peters to Goose Van Schaick, 1780 March 16; No. 1128
- Richard Peters to William Woodford, 1779 December 24; No. 1129
- Charles Pettit to the deputy quartermasters, 1780 October 2; No. 1130
- Charles Pettit to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 January 11; No. 1131
- Charles Pettit to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 April 12; No. 1132
- Thomas Pettit to Peter Van Brugh Livingston, 1776 June 1-30; No. 1133
- Lord William Fitzmaurice Petty Shelburne to Lord ________, 1767 October 6; No. 1134
- Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Board of Health to Sarah Zanes, 1808 January 23; No. 1135
- John Pickering, Jr. to Josiah Bartlett, 1774 June 21; No. 1136
- Timothy Pickering, Sr. "to my Brethren in the 13 United American Colonys or States", 1777 June 6; No. 1137
- Timothy Pickering to Thomas Cogswell, 1780 October 5; No. 1138
- Timothy Pickering to Thomas Evans, 1804 February 4; No. 1139
- Timothy Pickering to John Fisher, 1781 June 15; No. 1140
- Timothy Pickering to Tench Francis, 1799 August 31; No. 1141
- Timothy Pickering to Samuel Hodgdon, 1798 August 28; No. 1142
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 May 1; No. 1143
- Timothy Pickering, by order of the Board of War to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 June 3; No. 1144
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 June 12; No. 1145
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 June 26; No. 1146
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1779 April 24; No. 1147
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1779 May 20; No. 1148
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1779 November 11; No. 1149
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 April 18; No. 1150
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 April 19; No. 1151
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 May 3; No. 1152
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 June 17; No. 1153
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 August 11; No. 1154
- Timothy Pickering to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 August 19; No. 1155
- Timothy Pickering to his son (Timothy Pickering III), 1799 January 25; No. 1156
- Timothy Pickering to Ralph Pomeroy, 1783 January 16; No. 1157
- Timothy Pickering to Adam Stephen, 1777 October 30; No. 1158
- Timothy Pickering to David Wolfe, 1785 April 13; No. 1159
- Timothy Pickering to ________, 1783 October 13; No. 1160
- United States, Continental Army, Quartermaster Department, 1783 April 18-June 10; No. 1161
- John Pigeon, Jr. to Henry Jackson, 1777 December 1; No. 1162
- Timothy Pickering to the Commissioners of the Treasury, 1788 May 24; No. 1163
- William Pitt (later Lord Chatham)to the Governor of New Hampshire (Benning Wentworth), 1758 December 9; No. 1164
- Lord William Pitt Chatham to ________, 1776 March 9; No. 1165
- Pierre-Nicholas-Charles, comte de Dalet to the Continental Congress, Philadelphia, 1775 January 8; No. 1166
- Martha Poor to the Committee on Soldier Accounts, 1783 January 13; No. 1167
- Rhode Island, Town of Portsmouth to the General Assembly, 1784 October 28; No. 1168
- Robert Prescott to Peter Lewis Perrin, 1768 November 22; No. 1169
- Augustine Prevost to Benjamin Lincoln, 1779 January 29; No. 1170
- James Mark Prevost to Thomas Pinckney, 1779 February 5; No. 1171
- Edward Proctor to David Jeffries, 1780 June 19; No. 1172
- Proposals for Monarchy in America, 1787 June 28; No. 1173
- Israel Putnam to Aaron Burr, 1777 July 14; No. 1174
- Israel Putnam to William Livingston, 1777 April 25; No. 1175
- Israel Putnam to Matthew Fairfield, 1783 January 29; No. 1176
- Allen Quynn, 1776 May 26; No. 1177
- Johann Gottlieb Rall, by order of Gen. Sir William Howe, 1776 December; No. 1178
- Johann Gottlieb Rall, by order of Gen. Sir William Howe, 1776 December; No. 1179
- David Ramsay to the Governor of Rhode Island (John Collins), 1786 February 1; No. 1180
- Nathaniel Ramsay to Mordecai Gist, 1784 March 15; No. 1181
- Edmund Randolph to Edward Carrington, 1791 March 8; No. 1182
- Edmund Randolph to George Hammond, 1795 March 7; No. 1183
- Edmund Randolph to John Jay or Thomas Pinckney or William Allen Deas, 1795 March 7; No. 1184
- Edmund Randolph to the Speaker of the House of Delegates Benjamin Harrison, 1786 December 28; No. 1185
- Edmund Randolph, 1788 September 27; No. 1186
- State of Delaware, Newcastle County Court to Gunning Bedford, 1780 July 4; No. 1187
- George Read to Gunning Bedford, 1782 February 12; No. 1188
- Joseph Read to James Mott, 1786 April 26; No. 1189
- Virginia, 1776 September 10; No. 1190
- Joseph Reed to Frederick Antis, 1780 May 26; No. 1191
- Joseph Reed to George Johnstone, 1778 June 13; No. 1192
- Joseph Reed to Friedrich Wilhelm, 1778 September 29; No. 1193
- George Reid to John Nesmith, 1780 August 18; No. 1194
- Great Britain, Navy, n.d.; No. 1195
- Penobscot Expedition, 1779 August 6; No. 1196
- Militia Election, 1781 September 12; No. 1197
- John Reynolds to Henry Jackson, 1778 November 27; No. 1198
- Colony of Rhode Island, General Assembly, 1776 June; No. 1199
- Elisha Rhodes, 1780 October 1; No. 1200
- Jujardy de Granville, ______ Tallet, and John Bryan, 1782 August 20; No. 1201
- Oliver Rice to Jonathan Rice, 1779 January 26; No. 1202
- Oliver Rice to Jonathan Rice, 1779 April 22; No. 1203
- Oliver Rice to Jonathan Rice, 1779 October 13; No. 1204
- Oliver Rice to Jonathan Rice, 1779 November 23; No. 1205
- Oliver Rice to Jonathan Rice, 1782 March 9; No. 1206
- Oliver Rice to Jonathan Rice, 1782 October 23; No. 1207
- Oliver Rice to Jonathan Rice, 1782 November 15; No. 1208
- Oliver Rice to Jonathan Rice, 1783 December 25; No. 1209
- John Roberts, 1781 February 1; No. 1210
- Addison Richardson to his wife, 1776 November 14; No. 1211
- James Ridge to Sir John Bridges, 1792 July 4; No. 1212
- William Ripley, 1777 August 19; No. 1213
- Rivington and Van Horne to James Rivington, 1796 April 7; No. 1214
- Daniel Roberdeau, 1762 January 12; No. 1215
- James Robertson to Walter Rutherford, 1777 December 4; No. 1216
- Caleb Robinson, 1782 May 9; No. 1217
- Donatien-Marie-Joseph de Vimeur, vicomte de Rochambeau to "Les Ministres", 1795 April 22, May 9; No. 1218
- Jean-Baptiste de Vimeur, comte de Rochambeau to M. de Morangis de St. Albon, 1767 October 10; No. 1219
- Jean-Baptiste-Donatien de Vimeur, comte de Rochambeau to ________, 1788 June 11; No. 1220
- Jean-Baptiste-Donatien de Vimeur, comte de Rochambeau to ________, 1779 July 27; No. 1221
- Caesar Rodney to Thomas Rodney, 1772 March 31; No. 1222
- Caesar Rodney to Thomas Rodney, 1776 May 8; No. 1223
- Caesar Rodney to Thomas Rodney, 1776 November 18; No. 1224
- Lord George Rodney to Henry Dundas, 1799 October 21; No. 1225
- Hezekiah Rogers to William Linnard, 1808 December 12; No. 1226
- John Roosevelt and Nicholas J. Roosevelt to John Vanwie, 1781 October 22; No. 1227
- George Ross, n.d.; No. 1228
- George Ross, Administrator of Margaret Neilson, deceased to the justices of the Orphans' Court for Lancaster County, Pa., 1759 September 4; No. 1229
- George Ross to John Miller, 1766 October 24; No. 1230
- James Ross to Israel Shreve, 1795 January 15; No. 1231
- James Ross to Israel Shreve, 1797 August 3; No. 1232
- James Ross to Israel Shreve, 1798 October 26; No. 1233
- James Ross to Jonathan Smith, 1800 June 5; No. 1234
- Hugh Runyan to Moore Furman, 1779; No. 1235
- John Rutherford to Andrew Bell, 1794 May 6; No. 1236
- Edward Rutledge to Catherine Littlefield Greene, 1789 December 15; No. 1237
- John Rutledge to the treasurer, 1779 August 2; No. 1238
- Arthur St. Clair to the Pennsylvania Committee of Safety, 1775-1776; No. 1239
- Arthur Brown, 1779 September 7; No. 1240
- Emmanuel-Henri-Oswald-Joseph-Nicholas-Leipold, prince de Salm-Salm to Jean-Baptiste-Donatien de Vimeur, comte de Rochambeau, 1784 March 2; No. 1241
- Zephaniah Platt and Jonathan? Lawrence, 1777 April 29; No. 1242
- Samuel Sargent to Curtis and Peter Grub, 1779 November 11; No. 1243
- William Satterlee, 1782 May 7; No. 1244
- Benjamin Franklin, and others, 1779 March 26; No. 1245
- David Sayles, 1779 September 16; No. 1246
- Philip Schuyler to George Clinton, 1778 June 6; No. 1247
- Philip Schuyler to John Jay, 1785 May 4; No. 1248
- Philip Schuyler to Benjamin Lincoln, 1777 August 13; No. 1249
- Philip Schuyler to Artemus Ward, 1776 December 8; No. 1250
- Philip Schuyler to Marinus Willet, 1778 March 22; No. 1251
- Philip Schuyler to Abraham Yates, Jr., 1793 September 25; No. 1252
- Philip Schuyler to Abraham Yates, Jr., 1793 September 27; No. 1253
- Isaac Sears to Roger Sherman, Eliphalet Dyer, and Silas Deane, 1775 November 28; No. 1254
- Isaac Sears to Messrs. Aspinwall and Smith, 1773 August 21; No. 1255
- Benjamin Seawell, 1780 October 14; No. 1256
- John Sullings to Henry Jackson, 1775 December 2; No. 1257
- John Semple, and others to John Hay, treasurer, 1782? January; No. 1258
- William Shannon to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 March 15; No. 1259
- Daniel Shaw and James Felton, selectman, 1777 March 31; No. 1260
- Roger Sherman to Jonathan Trumbull, Jr., 1780 January 8; No. 1261
- Roger Sherman to ________, n.d.; No. 1262
- Roger Sherman, 1761 April; No. 1263
- Edward Shippen to Jasper Yeates, 1783 July 5; No. 1264
- Israel Shreve to Mary Cokely Shreve, 1794 September 4; No. 1265
- Molyneux Shuldham to Paul Henry Curry, 1780 July 11; No. 1266
- Molyneux Shuldham to Paul Henry Curry, 1780 July 17; No. 1267
- Molyneux Shuldham to Paul Henry Curry, 1780 October 23; No. 1268
- Joseph Simon to William French, 1778 December 25; No. 1269
- James Simson, 1785 November 18; No. 1270
- Daniel Skinner, Jr., constable to Joseph Spencer, 1782 June 10; No. 1271
- Frederick Sliker to George Washington, 1790 November 6; No. 1272
- William Smallwood to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 April 5; No. 1273